export const questionSetOne = [
  {
    question: "React is a _________.",
    answers: [
      "Web development Framework",
      "JavaScript Library",
      "jQuery",
      "Web Server",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which ReactJS function renders HTML to the web page?",
    answers: [
      "render()",
      "ReactDOM.render()",
      "renders()",
      "ReactDOM.renders()",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "JSX stands for _____.",
    answers: ["JSON", "JSON XML", "JavaScript XML", "JavaScript and AngularJS"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: " JSX allows us to write _____.?",
    answers: [
      "jQuery in React",
      "Angular Code in React",
      "MySQL in React",
      "HTML in React",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What are Props?",
    answers: [
      "Props are arguments passed into React components",
      "Props are functions in the ReactJS",
      "Props are used to returns multiple values from the function",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which method is used to generate lists?",
    answers: ["map()", "generate()", "new()", "maps()"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
];

export const questionSetTwo = [
  {
    question: "What types of components do we have in ReactJS?",
    answers: [
      "Variable and Const components",
      "Class and Function components",
      "Method and Function components",
      "Array and Object components",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which statement is required to define a class component?",
    answers: [
      "extends React.Components",
      "imports React.Components",
      "extends React.Component",
      "imports React.Component",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Can components be passed as props?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "In ReactJS, what is State?",
    answers: [
      "It's a temporary storage of the elements",
      "It's a state of the execution of the ReactJS application",
      "It's an internal storage of the components",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
    answers: [
      "1 Element",
      "More than 1 element",
      "React does not return element",
      "None of the mentioned",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following methods is not a part of ReactDOM?",
    answers: [
      "ReactDOM.hydrate()",
      "ReactDOM.destroy()",
      "ReactDOM.createPortal()",
      "All of the mentioned",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
];

export const questionSetThree = [
  {
    question:
      "What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    answers: [
      "Original DOM",
      "Virtual DOM",
      "Both A and B.",
      "None of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following keyword is used to create a class inheritance?",
    answers: ["Create", "Inherits", "Extends", "This"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the declarative way to render a dynamic list of components based on values in an array?",
    answers: [
      "Using the reduce array method",
      "Using the <Each /> component",
      "Using the Array.map() method",
      "With a for/while loop",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the two ways to handle data in React?",
    answers: [
      "State & Props",
      "Services & Components",
      "State & Services",
      "State & Component",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Does React.js create a VIRTUAL DOM in the memory?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Reconciliation?",
    answers: [
      "The process through which React deletes the DOM",
      "The process through which React updates and deletes the component",
      "It is a process to set the state",
      "The process through which React updates the DOM",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
];

export const questionSetFour = [
  {
    question: "Who developed React.js?",
    answers: ["Apple", "Facebook", "Twitter", "Google"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Life cycle of components methods falls under following categories?",
    answers: [
      "Mounting, Unmounting",
      "Mounting, Updating",
      "Updating, Unmounting",
      "Mounting, Updating, Unmounting",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "React.js covers only the view layer of the app.",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the DOM?",
    answers: [
      "Document Object Model",
      "Data Object Model",
      "Data Option Model",
      "Documentation Object Model",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "React components can be?",
    answers: [
      "UseState, Stateless",
      "Statefull, Stateless",
      "Unstatefull Statefull",
      "None of these",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Can we write a comment in SVG file?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
];
